圣诞宝贝
Santa baby,
悄悄地把貂皮大衣放在圣诞树下给我吧
slip a sable under the tree, For me.
我一直都是非常好的女孩 圣诞宝贝
I’ve been an awful good girl, Santa baby,
今晚快从烟囱下来
hurry down the chimney tonight.
还有一台54年的敞篷车
Santa baby, a 54 convertible too,
淡蓝色的
Light blue.
我等你 亲爱的
I'll wait up for you dear.
圣诞宝贝
Santa baby,
今晚快从烟囱下来
hurry down the chimney tonight.
想想那些我错过的乐趣
Think of all the fun I've missed,
想想那些我还没亲过的费拉
Think of all the fellas that I haven't kissed,
明年我可能也会是好女孩
Next year I could be also good,
如果你满足所有我想要的圣诞礼物
If you'll check off my Christmas list,
圣诞甜心 我想要一台游艇
Santa honey, I wanna yacht,
不过这个要求真的不多
And really that's not a lot,
我今年整年都像天使一样
I’ve been an angel all year,
圣诞宝贝
Santa baby,
今晚快从烟囱下来
hurry down the chimney tonight.
圣诞好人
Santa cutie,
还有一件东西我真的想要
one thing I really do need,
一份地契
The deed
有白金矿的那种
To a platinum mine,
圣诞好人
Santa cutie,
今晚快从烟囱下来
hurry down the chimney tonight.
圣诞宝贝
Santa baby,
用复式别墅
fill my stocking with a duplex,
和支票塞满我的袜子吧
And checks.
记得要在上面签名
Sign your 'X' on the line,
圣诞宝贝
Santa baby
今晚快从烟囱下来
hurry down the chimney tonight.
来装饰我的圣诞树吧
Come and trim my Christmas tree,
要用从蒂芬妮买来的装饰
With some decorations bought at Tiffany's,
我真的相信你的存在
I really do believe in you,
让我看看你是否信任我
Let's see if you believe in me,
圣诞宝贝
Santa baby,
忘了和你提一件小东西
forgot to mention one little thing,
一个戒指
A ring.
我不是指那个电话的铃哦
I don't mean on the phone,
圣诞宝贝
Santa baby,
今晚快从烟囱下来
Hurry down the chimney tonight
快点快点
Hurry, hurry
今晚快从烟囱下来
Hurry down the chimney tonight
快点快点
Hurry, hurry
今晚快从烟囱下来
Hurry down the chimney tonight
快 就今晚
Hurry, tonight